So you want to know more about belly dancing?
Hi, I Johanna Krynytzky with Hip Expressions Dance Studio.
So how would you describe belly dancing?
What is belly dancing really all about?
It's a dance of celebration.
It's a dance where you're learning to move around and to be comfortable with your body.
It's a dance of isolation.
So it's isolating one part of your body without moving the other part.
Ultimately, it's putting altogether in to a dance that's interpreting the music.
So it's really about the music that inspires you to move.
Now belly dancing can be done as a performance art.
Entertainment, restaurants, weddings, all sorts of different parties, special events you can have a belly dancer.
Or belly dancing can be done just for yourself personally; in your own home, in your living room, at the dance studio.
It's really just about expressing yourself and your emotions.
So belly dancing really is all about that personal expression through using your body.
I'm Johanna Krynytzky with Hip Expression Belly Dance studio, telling you about belly dancing.